thinkorswim.com 2012-09-11

# 

                                                                                                                        Rev.
                      WHAT DOES TD AMERITRADE
 FACTS                DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
 Why?                 Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
                      consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you
                      how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to
                      understand what we do.
 What?                The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you
                      have with us. This information can include:
                      n     Social Security number and financial account numbers
                      n     Account balances and transaction information
                      n     Income and employment information
 How?                 All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday
                      business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their
                      customers’ personal information; the reasons TD Ameritrade chooses to share; and whether
                      you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information                  Does TD Ameritrade share?    Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes—
such as to process your transactions, maintain
                                                                          Yes                            No
your account(s), respond to court orders and legal
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes—
                                                                          Yes                            No
to offer our products and services to you
For joint marketing with other financial companies                        No                      We do not share
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                          Yes                            No
information about your transactions and experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                          No                      We do not share
information about your creditworthiness
For our affiliates to market to you                                       Yes                            Yes
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                        No                      We do not share
 To limit             n     Call 800-326-7141—a client services representative will assist you or
 our sharing          n     Visit us online: tdameritrade.com/privacy
                      Please note:
                      If your account is managed by an independent investment advisor, your account preferences are
                      already set to limit our sharing.
                      If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we
                      sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as
                      described in this notice.
                      However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
 Questions?           Call 800-326-7141 or email privacy@tdameritrade.com
                                                          Page 1 of 2                                    AMTD 800 F 05/12

  Page 2
  Who we are
  Who is providing this notice?                                        TD Ameritrade, Inc. and the TD Ameritrade family of divisions and companies,
                                                                       including TD Ameritrade Institutional, thinkorswim, and Amerivest Management, LLC.
  What we do
  How does TD Ameritrade                                               To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we
  protect my personal information?                                     use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include
                                                                       computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
                                                                       For more information, please visit tdameritrade.com/security
  How does TD Ameritrade                                               We collect your personal information, for example, when you
  collect my personal information?                                     n     Open an account or make deposits or withdrawals from your account
                                                                       n     Direct us to buy securities or direct us to sell your securities
                                                                       n     Tell us about your investment or retirement portfolio
                                                                       We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit
                                                                       bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
  Why can’t I limit all sharing?                                       Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                                                       n 	Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information
                                                                             about your creditworthiness
                                                                       n     Affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                                                       n     Sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                                                       State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to
                                                                       limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.
  What happens when I limit sharing
  for an account I hold jointly with                                   Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
  someone else?
  Definitions
  Affiliates                                                           Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                                                                       nonfinancial companies.
                                                                       n 	Our affiliates include companies with a TD Ameritrade name, financial companies
                                                                             such as RED Option Advisors, Inc. and the TD Bank Financial Group family, including
                                                                             TD Bank and The Toronto-Dominion Bank, as well as non-financial companies such
                                                                             as Investools, Inc.
  Nonaffiliates                                                        Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                                                       financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                                                       n 	TD Ameritrade does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
  Joint marketing                                                      A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together
                                                                       market financial products or services to you.
                                                                       n     TD Ameritrade doesn’t jointly market.
  Other important information
For Nevada Residents. We are providing you this notice pursuant to state law. You may be placed on our internal Do Not Call List by calling 800-326-7141. Nevada law requires
that we also provide you with the following contact information: Bureau of Consumer Protection, Office of the Nevada Attorney General, 555 E. Washington St., Suite 3900,
Las Vegas, NV 89101; Phone number: 702-486-3132; email: BCPINFO@ag.state.nv.us.
For Vermont Residents. In accordance with Vermont law, we will not share information we collect about Vermont residents with companies who are not affiliates, except as
permitted by law, such as with your consent or to service your accounts. We will not share information about your creditworthiness with our affiliates without your authorization or
consent, but we may share information about our transactions or experiences with you with our affiliates without your consent.
For California Residents. In accordance with California law, we will not share information we collect about you with nonaffiliates, except as allowed by law. For example, we may
share information with your consent or to service your accounts. Among our affiliates, we will limit information sharing to the extent required by California law.
                                                                                     Page 2 of 2                                                                  AMTD 800 F 05/12
